## MICHAEL HEGNER

Midlothian VA, 23113 | Phone: 804-334-6993 | Email: <a href="https://github.com/hegner123">hegner123@gmail.com</a> Github: <a href="https://github.com/hegner123">https://github.com/hegner123</a> | Portfolio: <a href="https://www.michaelhegner.com/hegner123">https://github.com/hegner123</a> | Portfolio: <a href="https://www.michaelhegner.com/hegner123">https://www.michaelhegner.com/hegner123</a> | Portfolio: <a href="https://www.michaelhegner.com/hegner123">https://www.michaelhegner.com/hegner.c

#### SUMMARY

MERN Full Stack Web Developer with a background in Audio Engineering and a passion for problem solving. Experienced with creative troubleshooting under pressure. Valued for a detailed approach to learning new skills and an adaptable mindset, switching between tasks quickly and efficiently.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML, CSS, JS, MongoDB, SQL, Bootstrap

Applications: Firebase, Heroku, Github, VS Code, Polypane, Cpanel, PHP myAdmin

### **PROJECTS**

Pro-Project Studio | github.com/hegner123/pro-project-studio|pro-project-studio.herokuapp.com/

- The purpose of the app is to create a project management system for audio recording engineers. It's a one stop place for engineers to update the status of each song and to communicate that status with their clients.
- Mongo database, Node.js, Passport.js, Redux, React, React-data-grid, React-bootstrap.

#### EXPERIENCE

# Web Developer Freshmove Media

Oct 2019 – Present

Richmond, VA

- Held responsibilities as lead web developer working primarily with Wordpress websites.
- Facilitated design and implementation of clients vision.
- Worked with clients to overcome technical limitations and compromises.
- Migrated Websites from development servers to production servers.

# Producer/Recording Engineer Freelance Engineer

Nov 2011 - Present **Richmond**. VA

- Worked in recording studios as a Freelance Engineer including Spacebomb Studios.
- Acted as Recording Engineer and Mixing Engineer for Julien Baker's debut record "Sprained Ankle".
- Comfortable interpreting a client's artistic vision and building an overview of the technical processes needed to achieve that vision.

#### EDUCATION

Bootcamp Certificate: University of Richmond, Richmond, VA, July 2019 - February 2020

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

**B.S. Recording Industry/ Audio Production:** Middle Tennessee State University, Murfreesboro, TN